# Diego Cattaneo

Frontend Developer Buenos Aires, Argentina

diegocattaneo@hotmail.com.ar \$\infty\$+54 9 11 2251 8731

As a frontend developer with more than 2 years experience working with React and Typescript, and some backend skills using Node.js, I enjoy creating quality products to provide a good user experience, following best practices, which are essential for writing efficient, clean and reusable code.

## **Experience**

Frontend Developer - Instituto Nacional de Tecnología Industrial (INTI)

Jan 2023 - Present

- I have worked with the team in the redesign and rebuild of the web application, as well as in its ongoing maintenance and improvement.
- Collaborating on user experience improvements in order to increase their engagement.
- Web Developer Freelance

Mar 2021 - Dec 2022

• Custom websites developed for clients as a freelancer using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and nonrelational databases according to their needs.

#### Education

Degree in Computer Science - UNLAM

Jan 2016 - Dec 2022

# Languages

- Spanish
- **English**

## **Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React

- Typescript
- Tailwind
- Git
- Context API

- Node
- Express
- Mongo & Firebase
- MySQL